How can I create great sponsorships for my golf tournament you cry?
Well, no worries because that's exactly what this segment is about.
Let's take a look at some of the perks you can offer potential sponsors.
To begin with, you can utilize your very own golf program that you're going to be printing.
Now, depending on the size of the sponsorship, you can offer quarter page, half page, or full-page ads.
Title sponsors might get advertisement on the front the back cover of the actual program.
Another great perk; offer a vendor table at the event.
Companies will love the idea that they get to interact with the actual golfers at the event.
Now, lets not forget your charity or event website.
This is a great place to promote your sponsors as well.
You can do this through banners, links to their website, or actual ads on your site promoting the sponsor.
Finally, I hope you're going to hand out lots and lots of flyers.
A flyer is a great way to promote the sponsor.
Again, depending on the level, they might just get their website listed.
If it's a large sponsor, they can have their logo or their full ad.
The more colorful and bright the flyer the better.
Remember sponsors are looking for potential customers, promotion, and publicity.
Also remember a happy sponsor is sure to come back year after year after year.